<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<similar>
	<info>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Radiohead]]></name>
			<type>music</type>
			<wTeaser><![CDATA[Radiohead are an English rock band from Abingdon, Oxfordshire, formed in 1985. The band consists of Thom Yorke (vocals, guitars, keyboards), Jonny Greenwood (guitars, keyboards, other instruments), Ed O'Brien (guitars, backing vocals), Colin Greenwood (bass) and Phil Selway (drums, percussion).Radiohead released their debut single "Creep" in 1992. The song was initially unsuccessful, but it became a worldwide hit several months after the release of their debut album, Pablo Honey (1993). Radiohead's popularity rose in the United Kingdom with the release of their second album, The Bends (1995). Radiohead's third album, OK Computer (1997), propelled them to greater international fame. Featuring an expansive sound and themes of modern alienation, OK Computer is often acclaimed as one of the landmark records of the 1990s.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Radiohead]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[Radiohead]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[http://www.youtube.com/v/lstDdzedgcE]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[lstDdzedgcE]]></yID>
		</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Fight Club]]></name>
			<type>book</type>
      <wTeaser><![CDATA[Fight Club is a 1999 American film based on the 1996 novel of the same name by Chuck Palahniuk. The film was directed by David Fincher and stars Edward Norton, Brad Pitt and Helena Bonham Carter. Norton plays the unnamed protagonist, an "everyman" who is discontented with his white-collar job. He forms a "fight club" with soap maker Tyler Durden, played by Pitt, and becomes embroiled in a relationship with him and a dissolute woman, Marla Singer, played by Bonham Carter.Palahniuk's novel was optioned by 20th Century Fox producer Laura Ziskin, who hired Jim Uhls to write the film adaptation. Fincher was one of four directors the producers considered and hired him because of his enthusiasm for the film. Fincher developed the script with Uhls and sought screenwriting advice from the cast and others in the film industry.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fight_Club_%28film%29]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
		</resource>
	</info>
	<results>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Lullaby]]></name>
			<type>book</type>
      <wTeaser><![CDATA[Lullaby is a horror-satire novel by American author Chuck Palahniuk, published in 2002. It won the 2003 Pacific Northwest Booksellers Association Award, and was nominated for the Bram Stoker Award for Best Novel in 2002. BackgroundIn 1999, Fred Palahniuk, Chuck's father, began dating an Idaho woman named Donna Fontaine. Fontaine had recently put her ex-husband, Dale Shackleford, in prison for sexual abuse, and Shackleford had vowed to kill Fontaine as soon as he was released from prison. After his release, Shackleford followed Fred Palahniuk and Fontaine home from a date to her apartment in Kendrick, Idaho. After shooting Fred Palahniuk in the abdomen and Fontaine in the back of the neck, Shackleford left them to die, though he allegedly returned to the scene multiple times to attempt to start a fire large enough to destroy the evidence.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lullaby_(novel)]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
    </resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Diary]]></name>
			<type>book</type>
      <wTeaser><![CDATA[Diary is a 2003 novel by Chuck Palahniuk. The book is written like a diary, its writer/narrator/main character is Misty Wilmot, a once-promising young artist currently working as a waitress in a hotel, although it never actually states who the narrarator is, it's safe to assume that it is Misty. Her husband, a contractor, is in a coma after a suicide attempt. According to the description on the back of Diary, Misty "soon finds herself a pawn in a larger conspiracy that threatens to cost hundreds of lives."Diary loosely falls into the modern horror genre, putting aside violence and shock tactics in favour of psychological scares and dark humor.The audio version of Diary is narrated by actress Martha Plimpton. Plot summaryDiary takes the form of a "coma diary" telling the story of Misty Marie Wilmot as her husband lies senseless in a hospital after a suicide attempt.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Diary_(novel)]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
    </resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Survivor]]></name>
			<type>book</type>
      <wTeaser><![CDATA[Survivor is a novel by Chuck Palahniuk, first published in February 1999. The book tells the story of Tender Branson, a member of the Creedish Church, a death cult. The chapters and pages are numbered backwards in the book, beginning with Chapter 47 on page 289 and ending with page 1 of Chapter 1. Plot overviewIn the book, every member of the Creedish Cult learns how to be a servant for the human race—most of them are butlers and maids—and fear most human pleasures. They await a sign from God to tell them to deliver themselves unto Him; that is, they must commit suicide.The sign finally comes, and a good ten years later, Tender becomes the last surviving member of the cult. He is thrown into mainstream culture and becomes a personal icon for many people.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Survivor_%28Chuck_Palahniuk_novel%29]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
    </resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Choke]]></name>
			<type>book</type>
      <wTeaser><![CDATA[Choke is a 2001 novel by American author Chuck Palahniuk. Plot summaryChoke follows Victor Mancini and his friend Denny through a few months of their lives with frequent flashbacks to the days when Victor was a child. He had grown up moving from one foster home to another, as his mother was found to be unfit to raise him. Several times throughout his childhood, his mother would kidnap him from his various foster parents, though every time they would eventually be caught, and he would again be remanded over to the governmental child welfare agency.In the present day setting of the book, Victor is now a man in his mid-twenties who left medical school in order to find work to support his feeble mother who is now in a nursing home.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Choke_(novel)]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
		</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Snuff]]></name>
			<type>book</type>

						<wTeaser><![CDATA[Snuff is a novel by Chuck Palahniuk that was released on May 20, 2008. Book descriptionCassie Wright, porn priestess, intends to cap her legendary career by breaking the world record for serial fornication porn movies, on camera, with six hundred men. Snuff unfolds through the perspectives of Mr. 600, Mr. 72, Mr. 137, and Wright's personal assistant, Sheila. With his satirical narrative and thorough research, Chuck Palahniuk reveals through these four characters the little-known facts and histories of not only pornography and sexual deviance, but also acting and life in and out of the spotlight, and throughout the novel shows the rarely acknowledged presence of pornography in modern America. First edition copiesThe first edition print of the books included a light brown color to the font, and as usual with Palahniuk's releases, a heavily themed jacket and inside cover for the book.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Snuff_%28Palahniuk_novel%29]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
																	</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Invisible Monsters]]></name>
			<type>book</type>

						<wTeaser><![CDATA[Invisible Monsters is a novel by Chuck Palahniuk, published in 1999. It is his third novel to be published, though it was his second written novel (after Insomnia: If You Lived Here, You'd Be Home Already). The novel was originally supposed to be Palahniuk's first novel to be published, but it was rejected by the publisher for being too disturbing. After the success of his novel Fight Club, Invisible Monsters was given a second chance, and a revised version of it was published. It is the only Palahniuk book not to be published in hardcover; the first edition is a paperback. It has since been adapted into a graphic novel by comic artist KGZ, a.k.a. Gabor Kiss. PlotThe story concerns a disfigured woman whose name is Shannon McFarland, frequently referred to by other names given to her by Brandy Alexander, with whom she spends the majority of the book.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Invisible_Monsters]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
																	</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Haunted]]></name>
			<type>book</type>

						<wTeaser><![CDATA[Haunted may refer to:]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Haunted_(novel)]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
																	</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Pygmy]]></name>
			<type>book</type>

						<wTeaser><![CDATA[Pygmy is an epistolary novel by Chuck Palahniuk. It was released on May 5, 2009. PlotThe plot revolves around a 13-year-old boy named Agent Number 67 from an unnamed, totalitarian state described as a "mash-up of North Korea, Cuba, Communist-era China, and Nazi-era Germany", as an exchange student to live with an American family from an unnamed Midwestern location as a sleeper agent to execute a terrorist attack on the United States codenamed "Operation Havoc". Nicknamed "Pygmy" by his American family for his diminutive size, he is introduced into the rituals of modern American life such as enrolling in public school, and going to church. On a trip to Wal-Mart with his host brother, in the bathroom he sodomises a bully who had been victimising his host brother.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Pygmy_(novel)]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
																	</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[American Psycho]]></name>
			<type>book</type>

						<wTeaser><![CDATA[American Psycho is a psychological thriller and satirical novel by Bret Easton Ellis, published in 1991. The story is told in the first person by the protagonist, serial killer and Manhattan businessman Patrick Bateman. The book's graphic violence and sexual content generated a great deal of controversy before and after publication. A film adaptation starring Christian Bale was released in 2000 to generally favorable reviews.The Observer notes that while "some countries [deem it] so potentially disturbing that it can only be sold shrink-wrapped", "critics rave about it" and "academics revel in its transgressive and postmodern qualities." In 2008, it was confirmed that producers Craig Roessler and Jesse Singer were developing a musical adaptation of the novel to appear on Broadway.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/American_Psycho]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
																	</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Trainspotting]]></name>
			<type>book</type>

						<wTeaser><![CDATA[Trainspotting is the first novel by Scottish writer Irvine Welsh. It takes the form of a collection of short stories, written in either Scots, Scottish English or British English, revolving around various residents of Leith, Edinburgh who either use heroin, are friends of the core group of heroin users, or engage in destructive activities that are implicitly portrayed as addictions that serve the same function as heroin addiction. The novel is set in the late 1980s and has been called "the voice of punk, grown up, grown wiser and grown eloquent". The novel has since achieved a cult status, added to by the global success of the film based on it, Trainspotting (1996), directed by Danny Boyle. Welsh later wrote a sequel, Porno, in 2002.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Trainspotting_%28novel%29]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
																	</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[The Rules Of Attraction]]></name>
			<type>book</type>

						<wTeaser><![CDATA[The Rules of Attraction is a dark comedy and satirical novel by Bret Easton Ellis published in 1987. The novel focuses on a handful of rowdy and often sexually promiscuous, spoiled Bohemian college students at a liberal arts college in 1980s New Hampshire, primarily focusing on three of them who find themselves in a love triangle. The novel is written in first person narrative, and the story is told from the points of view of various characters.The book was adapted into a film of the same name in 2002. Ellis himself has remarked that of all the film adaptations of his books, The Rules of Attraction came closest to capturing his sensibility and recreating the world he created in his novels. Plot summaryThe novel is written in the first-person, continuing the aesthetic of Ellis' earlier Less Than Zero, and is told from the points of view of multiple characters.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Rules_of_Attraction]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
																	</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Less Than Zero]]></name>
			<type>book</type>

						<wTeaser><![CDATA[Less Than Zero is a novel by Bret Easton Ellis, published in 1985. It was his first published effort, released while he was 21 and still in college. Plot summaryTitled after the Elvis Costello song of the same name, the novel follows the life of Clay, a rich young college student who has returned to his hometown of Los Angeles, California for the winter break during the early 1980s. He spends much of the novel going to parties and doing drugs with his friends. During this time, he must decide whether or not he wants to restart a relationship with Blair, for whom he is uncertain about his feelings. Meanwhile, Clay has one night stands with a few men and women on the side while his relationship with Blair goes downhill. At the same time, he attempts to renew his relationship with his best friend, Julian, who has become a prostitute and drug addict.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Less_Than_Zero_(book)]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
																	</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Sex, Drugs, And Cocoa Puffs: A Low Culture Manifesto]]></name>
			<type>book</type>

						<wTeaser><![CDATA[Sex, Drugs, and Cocoa Puffs: A Low Culture Manifesto is a book written by Chuck Klosterman, first published by Scribner in 2003. It is a collection of eighteen comedic essays on popular culture. OverviewKlosterman presents his essays as if they were tracks on a CD. Between each essay, or track, is an "interlude"—a short, entertaining blurb linking the essays. The following essays are included in Sex, Drugs, and Cocoa Puffs:]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Sex,_Drugs,_and_Cocoa_Puffs:_A_Low_Culture_Manifesto]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
																	</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[V For Vendetta]]></name>
			<type>book</type>

						<wTeaser><![CDATA[V for Vendetta is a ten-issue comic book series written by Alan Moore and illustrated mostly by David Lloyd, set in a dystopian future United Kingdom imagined from the 1980s to about the 1990s. A mysterious masked revolutionary who calls himself "V" works to destroy the totalitarian government, profoundly affecting the people he encounters. Warner Bros. released a film adaptation of V for Vendetta in 2005.The series depicts a near-future UK after a nuclear war, which has left much of the world destroyed, though most of the damage to the country is indirect, via floods and crop failures. In this future, a fascist party called Norsefire has exterminated its opponents in concentration camps and now rules the country as a police state. V, an anarchist revolutionary dressed in a Guy Fawkes mask, begins an elaborate, violent, and intentionally theatrical campaign to murder his former captors, bring down the government, and convince the people to rule themselves.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/V_for_Vendetta]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
																	</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Glamorama]]></name>
			<type>book</type>

						<wTeaser><![CDATA[Glamorama is a novel by American writer Bret Easton Ellis. It was published by Alfred A. Knopf in 1998. Unlike Ellis' previous novels, Glamorama is set in and satirizes the 1990s, specifically celebrity culture and consumerism. Time describes the novel as "a screed against models and celebrity." DevelopmentEllis wanted to write a Stephen King-style ghost story novel, what would eventually become Lunar Park; finding it difficult at the time, he began work on the other novel which he had in mind. This was a Robert Ludlum-style thriller, with the intention of using one of his own vapid characters who lack insight as the narrator. Literary devices and themesThe novel is a satire of modern celebrity culture; this is reflected in its premise, which features models-turned-terrorists.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Glamorama]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
																	</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Fear And Loathing In Las Vegas]]></name>
			<type>book</type>

						<wTeaser><![CDATA[Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas: A Savage Journey to the Heart of the American Dream is an autobiographical novel by Hunter S. Thompson, illustrated by Ralph Steadman. The book is a roman à clef, rooted in autobiographical incidents. The story follows its protagonist, Raoul Duke, and his attorney, Dr. Gonzo, as they descend on Las Vegas to chase the American Dream through a drug-induced haze. The novel first appeared as a two-part series in Rolling Stone magazine in 1971, was printed as a book in 1972, and was later adapted into a film of the same name in 1998 by Terry Gilliam starring Johnny Depp and Benicio del Toro. OriginsThe novel Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas is based on two trips to Las Vegas, Nevada, that Hunter S.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fear_and_Loathing_in_Las_Vegas]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
																	</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Requiem For A Dream]]></name>
			<type>book</type>

						<wTeaser><![CDATA[Requiem for a Dream is a 1978 novel by Hubert Selby, Jr., that concerns four New Yorkers whose lives spiral out of control as they succumb to their addictions.This story follows the lives of Harry, Marion, Tyrone, and Sara, who are all searching for the key to their dreams, and in the process, they get flung into a devastating life of addiction. Harry and Marion are in love and Tyrone is their friend. Sara is Harry’s lonely, widowed mother. Sara’s dream is to be on television, and when a phone call from a casting company gets her hopes up, she spends the next few months on diet pills to lose weight. She becomes addicted and delirious, ends up in the hospital, and undergoes electroconvulsive therapy. Harry, Marion and Tyrone are heroin addicts who decide to make money by buying some uncut heroin and selling it.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Requiem_for_a_Dream_(novel)]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
																	</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[A Clockwork Orange]]></name>
			<type>book</type>

						<wTeaser><![CDATA[A Clockwork Orange is a 1962 dystopian novella by Anthony Burgess. The novel contains an experiment in language: the characters often use an argot called "Nadsat", derived from Russian.In 1998, the Modern Library ranked A Clockwork Orange 65th on its list of the 100 best English-language novels of the 20th century. Plot summaryAlex, a teenager living in near-future England, leads his gang on nightly orgies of opportunistic, random "ultra-violence." Alex's friends ("droogs" in the novel's Anglo-Russian slang, Nadsat) are Dim, a slow-witted bruiser who is the gang's muscle; Georgie, an ambitious second-in-command; and Pete, who mostly plays along as the droogs indulge their taste for ultra-violence. Alex is characterized as a sociopath and a hardened juvenile delinquent; he is nonetheless intelligent and quick-witted, with sophisticated taste in music.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/A_Clockwork_Orange]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
																	</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[A Scanner Darkly]]></name>
			<type>book</type>

						<wTeaser><![CDATA[A Scanner Darkly is a BSFA Award winning 1977 science fiction novel by American writer Philip K. Dick. The semi-autobiographical story is set in a dystopian Orange County, California, in the then-future of June 1994. It includes an extensive portrayal of drug culture and drug use (both recreational and abusive).The title echoes Through a Glass Darkly, a phrase from 1 Corinthians 13. SynopsisThe protagonist is Bob Arctor, member of a household of drug-users, who is also living a parallel life as Agent Fred, an undercover police agent assigned to spy on Arctor's household. Arctor/Fred shields his true identity from those in the drug subculture, and from the police themselves. (The requirement that narcotics agents remain anonymous, to avoid collusion and other forms of corruption, becomes a critical plot point late in the book.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/A_scanner_darkly]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
																	</resource>
		<resource>
			<name><![CDATA[Lunar Park]]></name>
			<type>book</type>

						<wTeaser><![CDATA[Lunar Park is a novel by Bret Easton Ellis with elements of faux autobiography and pastiche. It was released by Knopf on August 16, 2005. It is notable for being the first book written by Ellis to use past tense narrative. Plot summaryThe novel begins with an inflated and parodic but reasonably accurate portrayal of Ellis' early fame. It details incidents of his wild drug use and his publicly humiliating book tours to promote Glamorama. The novel dissolves into fiction as Ellis describes a liaison with an actress named Jayne Dennis, whom he later marries, and with whom he conceives an (initially) illegitimate child. From this point the fictional Ellis' life reflects the real Ellis' only in some descriptions of the past and possibly in his general sentiments.]]></wTeaser>
			<wUrl><![CDATA[http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Lunar_Park]]></wUrl>
			<yTitle><![CDATA[]]></yTitle>
			<yUrl><![CDATA[]]></yUrl>
			<yID><![CDATA[]]></yID>
																	</resource>
	</results>
</similar>
